FLORIAN PASQUEREAU

Software Engineer

PROFILE

Passionate about developments since 2011, I discovered it through the internet. The more I was developing, the more I wanted to get new skills, methods of work... That's why in 2015 I decided to make my passion my job, and become a software Engineer.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+33645134062

WEBSITE:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/florian-pasquereau-0988ab118/

EMAIL:

Florianpasquereau37@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

French Mother tongue English Professional German Beginner

EDUCATION

Ecole 42 Paris

11/2015 - 09/2018

Master degree in 2018: Learning development in C Cpp PHP MYSQL plus GIT Security on Unix environment

Joinery's School

09/2005 - 08/2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer (HONEYWELL)

09/2018-NOW

- Digitizing Order forms in a web base (Symfony DEVOPS unitest REACT JS)
- Extending the tracker to 7 Products (Symfony, MYSQL)
- Jira Plugin to manage configurations from JSON files (Java DEVOPS SYMFONY)
- Downloader to Easily share ISOs around the world (SYMFONY MYSQL REACT JS).
- Some Automations into SAP (JAVA/powershell)

Internship Software Engineer (HONEYWELL)

04/2018-09/2018

- Checksum for all ISO downloaded (QT Java)
- Tracker to 1 product (SYMFONY MYSQL)
- POC of a Downloader

Internship Web Developer (CODI ONE)

11/2016-05/2017

• Participating in the creation of several Websites

SKILLS

